People are still looking for a Luke Skywalker.
It's like, no, everybody is gonna have to be a part
of the fucking rebel force.
Like, everybody.
Well, and the fucking metaphor got lost in translation
when George Lucas wrote Star Wars, The Rebels.
That was the Viet Cong.
That was a metaphor for Vietnam.
And the empire, Darth Vader, was the US.
And everyone forgets that part.
And so we always, America in the movies-
We are the bad-
We root for the rebels in the movies
and we don't realize we're the empire in real life.
We're always the bad guys.
And so-
We are the dark force.
We are the dark army.
We are Voldemorts.
But the thing is, I don't know-
Expecto Patrona.
Like, I'm just saying, we're always the bad guys.
Like, in the never-ending story, we're the nothing.
Oh, we're going there.
Oh, man.
Adreyu!